

## PERSONAL DETAILS

Name and Surname: Laura Ortega

Studies: Degree in Business Studies

**Master in Audit** 

Nationality: Spanish

Age: **31** 

Marriage Status: Married
Current location: Abu Dhabi

E-mail: m.east.laura@gmail.com

Mobile phone: (+971) 056 7223356

## **Cover letter**

After finishing my studies in Business I completed a Master in Audit at the University of Zaragoza (Spain).

As a result, I started working for one recognized local Audit firm, where I joined as a trainee and become established soon after that. I worked there for four years and a half, learning and sharpening my analytical skills and working in different projects. My managers were very happy with my performance, but I had to leave the company for personal reasons.

If I have to define myself I would say that I am a self-starter, dynamic, responsible and always willing to learn and accept new challenges.

Below you will find a list of my skills and previous work experiences. I would love to provide you with more detailed information, so if you think I can fit into your organization please don't hesitate getting in touch with me.

I appreciate your time evaluating my application and I look forward hearing from you. Yours faithfully,

Laura Ortega

## **Knowledge**

### **Audit**

- Financial Audit (4 1/2 years)
  - Analysis of Balance Sheet and Income Statement of the Company to identify areas for review.
  - Evaluation of internal control of the Company to evaluate its reliability.
  - Calculation of materiality.
  - Identify and analyze risk areas performing the tests that we consider necessary to do.
  - Development of the work program.
  - Analysis of events after the year end that may affect the annual accounts.
  - Redaction of the auditor's report based in those adjusts and reclassifications which are higher the materiality, and in the events that could affect significatively to the comprehension of the annual accounts.

## **Finance-Banking**

- Commercial Manager
  - Attend to the customers in the bank cash.
  - Knowledge of financial products.
  - Sales.

## Computer Skills

- Office (Word, Excel, Access, Power Point, Outlook)
   Good Knowledge of all of them but especially good management of databases using Excel.
- Advanced user of Gesia (Audit management software widely used in Spain).
- Good Knowledge of Windows OS.

## Languages

- Spanish native spoken and written.
- **English** spoken and written high level. Until July 2013 I have attended to English classes every week at work, taught by native English teachers.
- French basic knowledge.

# **Driving license**

Obtained.

## **Experience**

### March 2008 - July 2013

Company: CGM Auditores – Zaragoza (Spain)

I worked as a technical in audit reporting to manager and team leads. Our main activities involved the gathering of relevant audit evidence in order to obtain a report according to the results thereof.

Audit work for Corporations, Nonprofit Organizations, Audit work of grants and Administrators of creditors meetings.

#### January-March 2008

Company: CGM Auditores - Zaragoza (Spain)

I completed the Master's Audit practices in CGM Auditores, where after the end of the trial period I was hired.

#### August 2007

Company: Santander Consumer Finance EFC – Zaragoza (Spain)

Before starting the Master in Auditing I worked at a summer replacement in Santander Consumer Finance supporting administrative functions and customer service.

#### October 2006 -July 2007

Company: Kintech Ingeniería S.L. – Zaragoza (Spain)

After completing my studies in Business I started working in this company dedicated to innovation in alternative energy systems. Occupying the position of administrative assistant attached to management I did work on financial accounting and cost accounting, capital management, delivery notes and invoices.

#### January- April 2006

Company: F&G Asesores Monzón S.L. - Monzón (Spain)

The work done was to introduce accounting entries of companies and arranged with banks and with the Tax Agency .

#### February- September 2005

Company: Caixa Penedés - Barbastro (Spain)

Until December 2004 I was doing for three months University practices in a bank office, after which I started working at another bank office of Caixa Penedés where I attended to the customers in the bank cash, sold financial products and managed capital.

### **Education**

### 2008 to July 2013

Attended at various courses with innovations that affects to accounts auditing, given by the "Institute of Certified Auditors of Spain" in Zaragoza and by the "Economists and Auditors' Register", and internal courses given by CGM Auditores firm where I worked.

### 2007-2008

Master in Audit. University of Zaragoza (Spain)

#### 2000-2006

Degree in Business Studies. University of Zaragoza - Campus of Huesca

### May-June 2006

English Course Callan School of English, London (40h).

#### 2005

Banking training course Caixa Penedés (100h).